[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor plays the character of Jeff Spicoli in the movie Fast Times at Ridgemont High?", "correct_answer": "Sean Penn", "incorrect_answers": ["Judge Reinhold", "Tom Cruise", "Nicolas Cage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I decided to return home, but when I walked in the front door there was a party in progress and my choreophobia caused me to panic yet again. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Dancing", "incorrect_answers": ["Balloons", "Loud music", "Crowds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did the Zodiac killer get his name and logo from?", "correct_answer": "A Watch Company", "incorrect_answers": ["A Gun Company", "The Astrological Symbol", "A White Supremacy Group"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following travels at the speed of light?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Radio rays", "Gamma rays", "X rays"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous rapper appeared in the movie 8 Mile as Male Lunch Truck Rapper?", "correct_answer": "Xzibit", "incorrect_answers": ["50 Cent", "Biggie", "2pac"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color was Leroys Glow at the end of the movie The Last Dragon?", "correct_answer": "gold", "incorrect_answers": ["blue", "purple", "red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Halkidiki, one of the Greek peninsulas, has a peculiar form which resembles what?", "correct_answer": "A trident", "incorrect_answers": ["A horseshoe", "An olive twig", "The Greek letter Omega"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrays Ernst Stavro Blofeld in the 1969 movie On Her Majestys Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "Telly Savalas", "incorrect_answers": ["John Gielgud", "Lorne Greene", "Peter Graves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name Ethan was the fourth most popular baby name of 2006, and means what?", "correct_answer": "Strong, optimistic", "incorrect_answers": ["Shepherd", "Intelligent, wise", "Of the forest"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why do doctors and dietitians recommend that we have five to nine fresh pieces of fruit a day?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Fruits stimulate the memory.", "Fruits help the organism release toxins.", "Fruits are rich in vital vitamins."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from the movie The Crow delivered the following words: Caw! Caw! Bang! Fuck, Im dead!\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Top Dollar", "incorrect_answers": ["Tin Tin", "T Bird", "Skank"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word can mean a social upstart or a social climber.", "correct_answer": "Rastaquouere", "incorrect_answers": ["Selcouth", "Zabern", "Pronk"]}]